MAX **ANDERSON**DESIGN & **DEVELOPMENT**

hiremaxwellanderson@gmail.com

Hello,

I am excited to apply for the available Web Development position available at Z Networks in Marysville, WA. I believe I have the combination of practical experience, technical ability, and problem solving spirit that you are looking for. I have several years experience in both design and development to include original content design for web and print media, web development and deployment, technical drafting and manufacturing specs. I enjoy taking projects from concept to delivery as a member of a cross-functional team. I have strong competencies in Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and associated web technologies. I have exposure to PHP with MySQL integration, and would be grateful for the opportunity to take a deep dive into PHP with your team.

Should you have any questions regarding my previous experience do not hesitate to reach out. I look forward to hearing from you soon to learn more about the position and how we might work together!

Best,

Max Anderson

MAX ANDERSON

DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

hiremaxwellanderson@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

SMT Operator Schippers & Crew, Inc. // Apr 2019 - Nov 2019

Operation of of automated assembly equipment in support of .5 million dollar contracts. Engaged in process improvement and engineering application development.

Design & Development Independent Contractor // Jul 2015 - Present Design and development services to include web development and asset production.

Inventory Manager Component Concepts, Inc. // May 2016 - Jul 2017

Managed company assets and stock inventory to include quality assurance and calibration tasks. Engaged in process improvement and lean production implementation.

EDUCATION

BAS Application Development North Seattle College

Spring 2019 - Spring 2021

Web Application Development Edmonds Community College

Summer 2018 - Spring 2019

CS & Design Technology University of Idaho

Summer 2010 - Spring 2013

ENGAGEMENT

Construction Crew Global Village Honduras // Aug 2018

Participated in the construction of a single family home for local family in Gracias Lempira, Honduras as part of local Habitat for Humanity affiliate.

Construction Crew Habitat for Humanity Snohomish County // Nov 2017 – Present Regularly participate in local housing projects for in-need families with the Snohomish County Habitat affiliate. Currently building 2 story home in Gold Bar, WA.

Technology Resource Navigator AmeriCorps Washington // Oct 2017 – Apr 2018 Worked to remove significant barriers to employment and economic opportunity through essential skills training. Led computer basics workshops of up to 12 people including one-one assistance.

COMPETENCIES

Strong Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Linux **Capable** Node/Express, Java, SQL, Bash, Git **Exposure** PHP, Django, Vue.js, APIs

MAX **ANDERSON**

DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

hiremaxwellanderson@gmail.com

REFERENCES

Amer Hadzikadunic

COO, Schippers & Crew amer@schippers.com

Jasmin Milak

Engineering Manager jasmin.milak@comcast.net

Morgan Blair

Associate Designer morganblairvtd@gmail.com